question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "hard",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Super Mario and Paarthurnax (Skyrim) are voiced by the same actor.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Sonic the Hedgehog universe, Tails; real name is Miles Prower.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In the Resident Evil series, Leon S. Kennedy is a member of STARS.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Mortal Kombat was almost based on Jean-Claude Van Damme movie.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Super Mario World, the rhino mini-boss, Reznor, is named after the lead singer of the band &quot;Nine Inch Nails&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Unturned originally started as a Roblox game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In the Super Mario series, the character Pauline is a Princess like Princess Peach.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Amazon acquired Twitch in August 2014 for $970 million dollars.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
